Gerry Mulligan Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 1-148, 160)
  - Forty days
    - Part (baritone saxophone), From "Brubeck parts" folder (Box-folder 82/1)
  - Forty five degree angle, Denzil Best
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/1)
  - Forty second and Broadway
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), On folder: revised 2/26/86 (Box-folder 128/4)
    - Parts (baritone saxophone, bass), GM personal performance parts (Box-folder 116)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), On folder: revised 2/26/86 (Box-folder 40/5)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Part (bass only), From "Standards" folder (Box-folder 18/19)
    - Lead sheet; sketch, On verso: sketch for K-4 Pacific (Box-folder 17/4)
  - Four and one Moore
    - Score (octet), On folder: "Songbook" album, sax section scores by Bill Holman (Box-folder 135/7)
    - Parts (octet), On folder: Saxes arr., "Mulligan Songbook" album, (originals) (Box-folder 56/6)
  - Four for three
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 18/7)
  - Fragments of Alice, Harry Freedman
    - Lead sheets, Laid in: typed letter to Gerry Mulligan from Freedman (Box-folder 22/17)
  - Franca arrivo, Earlier title: Rico apollo
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheets, On folder: Carriage House date 3/14/89 (Box-folder 21/12)
  - Freeway
    - Lead sheets; parts (Mulliganettes), At top of lead sheet: Chet Baker (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Friendly neighborhood dump
    - Lead sheet, For the Mel Tormé vocal compilation "Tentet with Tormé" (Box-folder 62/6)
  - The frugal horn
    - Score; sketch; parts (Box-folder 68/7)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/5)
  - Fun house
    - Lead sheets; sketches, From "Misc. sextet parts" folder (Box-folder 19/1)
  - G blues
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 121/10)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 32/6)
  - G. W.'s blue imp, George Wein
    - Sketch of score; parts, From "Synclavier" folders (Box-folder 20/12)
  - G.A.F.
    - Score (brass, rhythm), For commercial (Box-folder 145/6)
    - Parts (brass, rhythm), For commercial (Box-folder 5/5)
  - Gemini, Jimmy Heath
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Gemini ascending [G minor prelude]
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 9/8)
    - Sketch (sextet) (Box-folder 9/8)
  - Gene Lee's bossa nova
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/3)
  - The Genii
    - Lead sheet with annotations (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Georgia on my mind, Hoagy Carmichael
    - Score (orchestra), On folder: symphonic arrangement by Gerry Mulligan, '91, orchestral scores (Box-folder 144/6)
    - Score; sketch; solo part for Gerry (Orchestra), On folder: Rochester Philharmonic, 5/19-20/1989, arr John Dankworth (Box-folder 144/4)
    - Score; parts (Orchestra), On folder: Rochester Philharmonic, 5/19-20/1989, arr John Dankworth (Box-folder 108/3)
    - Score (orchestra), On folder: John Dankworth arrangement (Box-folder 110/5)
    - Sketch (Box-folder 19/9)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: symphonic arrangement by Gerry Mulligan, '91, strings, ww, brass, perc. (Box-folder 110/2)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: symphonic arrangement by Gerry Mulligan, '91, Synclavier score parts (Box-folder 110/3)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: symphonic arrangement by Gerry Mulligan, '91, rhythm section parts (Box-folder 110/4)
    - Sketches; notes (orchestra), On folder: symphonic arrangement by Gerry Mulligan, '91, notes and sketches for orchestral arr. (Box-folder 144/7)
  - Gerarny
    - Part (baritone saxophone), From "Brubeck parts" folder (Box-folder 82/1)
  - Gerry go round
    - Part (baritone saxophone), From "Brubeck parts" folder (Box-folder 82/1)
  - GM piano blues
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 145/9)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 28/4)
  - GM tune
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Get out of town, Cole Porter
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 18/6)
  - Ghosts
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 19/15)
    - Lead sheets, From studio session with Scott Hamilton for the recording Soft lights and sweet music (Box-folder 19/17)
  - A gift for Dizzy
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 128/2)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 40/2)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheet; sketches (Box-folder 23A/3)
  - Ginger bread boy, Jimmy Heath
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Girl friend, Shorty Rogers
    - Parts (alto sax), From "Shorty Rogers" folder (Box-folder 62/2)
  - Go home
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Bill Holman arrangement; Inscribed: March 1960, NYC (Box-folder 120/1)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Bill Holman arrangement (Box-folder 120/1)
    - Lead sheet (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 120/1)
  - Gold rush
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), On folder: Old big band chart (Box-folder 25/5)
  - Golden notebooks
    - Score; parts, Incomplete (Box-folder 135/2)
    - Score (Box-folder 135/2)
    - Parts (soprano saxophone, alto saxophone) (Box-folder 135/2)
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 9/2)
  - Gone
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 19/13)
  - Good neighbor Thelonious
    - Sketch; lead sheets, From "Synclavier" folders (Box-folder 20/9)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
  - Good places, Paul Beaver
    - Parts (Box-folder 8/6)
  - Goodbye John
    - Scores (tentet), Includes revisions (Box-folder 138/4)
    - Parts (tentet), From "Gig books" (Box-folder 113/8)
    - Parts (tentet), Revised parts and inserts (Box-folder 138/4)
    - Lead sheets; lyric sheets (Box-folder 22/30)
    - Lead sheet, On folder: 12/03/1991 (Box-folder 62/5)
  - Goodbye my love, Barry Manilow
    - Lead sheet; parts (piano, baritone saxophone) (Box-folder 19/4)
  - Grand tour
    - Score, Incomplete; On folder: Grand tour 172, L.A. different ens. orchestration (no score), minus 3rd trumpet (Box-folder 135/4)
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 135/3)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 135/3)
    - Parts (extra baritone saxophone) (Box-folder 80/2)
    - Sketch of lead sheet, Found in cue sheets for film La menace (Box-folder 53/7)
  - Grandma Moses
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Incomplete (Box-folder 127/7)
    - Sketches; notes (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 40/1)
    - Parts, From "Synclavier" folders (Box-folder 20/11)
    - Lead sheets, Yale jazz festival, 1988 (Box-folder 67/7)
  - Greg's tune, Greg Sauter
    - Part (solo baritone saxophone) (Box-folder 22/23)
  - Griffinity, Simon Pilbrow
    - Lead sheets, Note in GM's music library: Some good tunes from Australia (Box-folder 22/24)
  - Halfway to Spring
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheets (quartet), On folder: New songs for quartet 2/9/93, originals (Box-folder 23/7)
  - Hallo Jesus
    - Lead sheets; correspondence, Franco Petracchi arrangement (Box-folder 23A/4)
  - Hallucinations, Bud Powell
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 21/3)
  - Hank's prank, Hank Mobley
    - Lead sheet, From "Kai Winding" folder (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Happy birthday see also Holliday, Judy
    - Lead sheets; lyric sheets; scripts, Lyrics in the hand of Judy Holliday; Titles: All my life; I've got a friend; I want something lovely; My dad; Plain girls (Box-folder 14/4)
  - Harry's wild ride, From the 1967 film Luv
    - Score (Box-folder 133/1)
    - Parts (Box-folder 51/1)
  - Have you met Miss Jones, Shorty Rogers
    - Parts (tenor saxophone 1/2), From "Shorty Rogers" folder (Box-folder 62/2)
  - Here comes Mr. Jordan, Other title: Ohio traveler
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 21/8)
  - Here we go
    - Lead sheets with lyrics, Lyrics by Mary Brill (Box-folder 18/16)
  - Here's that rainy day
    - Lead sheet, From "Standards" folder (Box-folder 18/19)
  - Ho Capito
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 19/7)
  - Hold me
    - Lead sheet with lyrics, For the production play/musical Happy birthday (Box-folder 13/6)
    - Lead sheet, For the Mel Tormé vocal compilation "Tentet with Tormé" (Box-folder 62/6)
  - Holiday flight, Shorty Rogers
    - Parts (alto saxophone), From "Shorty Rogers" folder (Box-folder 62/2)
  - Holliday, Judy
    - Lyric sheets; sketches; notes, Lyrics in the hand of Holliday; see also Kinsey report and Happy birthday (Box-folder 14/2-3, 21/10)
  - Home, Van Steeden
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheets; sketches, On folder: Arr. ideas for Q (Box-folder 64/4)
  - Hong Kong blues, Eddie Sauter arrangement for Judy Holliday album
    - Score (big band) (Box-folder 117/1)
    - Parts (big band) (Box-folder 2/2)
  - Horatio at the well
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 20/3)
  - Horseshoe curve
    - Score (sextet), On folder: Sextet - 4 horn score by Jon Eardley (Box-folder 140/3)
  - Hospitality creek, Mitchel Forman
    - Lead sheets; notes by GM, Other titles in folder: Invention; Sundown flight; untitled (Box-folder 13/8)
  - Hot house, Tad Dameron
    - Lead sheet, In GM's hand (Box-folder 17/7)
  - House of the rising sun
    - Lead sheet (chords only) (Box-folder 13/5)
  - The house they never lived in
    - Lead sheets, From the 1977 film La menace (Box-folder 10/6)
  - The house they'll never live in
    - Lead sheets, GM notes regarding Rio in folder "Brazilian collection" (Box-folder 18/8)
  - How deep is the ocean, Irving Berlin
    - Lead sheets; sketches, On folder: Arr. ideas for Q (Box-folder 64/4)
  - I believe in you
    - Part (bass only), From "Standards" folder (Box-folder 18/19)
  - I can't believe you're in love with me
    - Score (Box-folder 136/3)
    - Score; parts (quartet) (Box-folder 62/8)
    - Score (11 piece big band), Mark Lopeman arrangement (Box-folder 137/9)
    - Parts (tentet), Mark Lopeman arrangement (Box-folder 137/9)
    - Part (bass, piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
  - I don't want to walk without you
    - Lead sheet, On folder: Arr. ideas for Q (Box-folder 64/4)
  - I follow you anywhere
    - Lead sheet, On folder: Carriage House date 3/14/89 (Box-folder 22/5)
  - I heard the shadows dancing, Earlier title: Franca arrivo
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 22/26)
    - Lead sheets; sketches (Box-folder 67/11)
    - Lead sheet; part (baritone saxophone), On folder: Formerly "Franca arrivo"; Carriage House date 3/14/89 (Box-folder 22/1)
  - I know, don't know how
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 145/10)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 46/1)
    - Lead sheets; parts (baritone saxophone, tenor saxophone), Sketches for "Walking shoes" on verso of baritone saxophone part (Box-folder 10/8)
    - Lead sheet, On folder: GM tunes/lead sheets, returned by Dave Brubeck, May 1984 (Box-folder 82/2)
  - I never was a young man
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 125/4)
    - Score (orchestra), On folder: Used in Houston with E. Kunzel, 2/5/87 (Box-folder 81/2)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: Used in Houston with E. Kunzel, 2/5/87 (Box-folder 81/3)
    - Parts (rhythm, solo parts) (Box-folder 58/4)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheets; lyric sheets (Box-folder 15/7)
  - I only have eyes for Flo
    - Parts (big band), For Boyd Raeburn Orchestra (Box-folder 8/2)
  - I remember Clifford, Benny Golson
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/2)
  - I want something lovely
    - Lead sheet with lyrics, From the play/musical Happy birthday (Box-folder 13/6)
  - I want to live: Black nightgown, Johnny Mandel
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Trumpet 1 part is missing (Box-folder 50/6)
  - I want to live: Theme, Johnny Mandel
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band), Original parts for film and album; GM score arrangement from July 1970 (Box-folder 132/2)
    - Score, On folder: Original score (Box-folder 132/1)
  - I want to live: Barbara's theme, Johnny Mandel
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), At top: "6/4 theme" crossed out, replaced with "Barbara's theme" (Box-folder 50/7)
  - I yi yi yi / How many hearts
    - Lyric sheets, Lyrics found with Paul Desmond music/lyrics (Box-folder 18/15)
  - I'd rather lead a band, Irving Berlin
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Tom Boras arrangement (Box-folder 148/5)
    - Score; sketch; parts (Concert Jazz Band), Note in GM's music library: Revised vocal arrangement, 12/86 (Box-folder 128/7)
    - Parts (baritone saxophone), GM personal performance parts and bass part (Box-folder 116)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Tom Boras arrangement (Box-folder 38/3)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), GM "Synclavier" arrangement (Box-folder 44/4)
    - Sketch for introduction, On folder: New intros in progress (Box-folder 140/7)
  - Ideas for big and small band
    - Score; sketches; notes (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 129/6)
  - Ide's side, Alternate title: Chant
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 122/5)
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band), Incomplete; GM arrangement (Box-folder 123/5)
    - Parts (tenor saxophone, baritone saxophone), From "Shorty Rogers" folder (Box-folder 62/2)
  - Idol gossip
    - Parts (sextet), Marciac festival sextet, 1993 (Box-folder 13/9)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 13/9)
    - Sketch for introduction, On folder: New intros in progress (Box-folder 140/7)
  - If I know how to be, Judy Holliday
    - Sketch; lyric sheets (Box-folder 14/3)
  - If I say I love you
    - Sketches, Laid in: lyric sheets (Box-folder 13/1)
  - If you can't beat 'em
    - Lead sheet; sketches (Box-folder 13/5)
  - If you could see me now
    - Lead sheets, From "Kai Winding" folder (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Igloo
    - Score; parts (sextet), On folder: Sextet - 4 horn scores by Jerry Hurwitz (Lloyd) (Box-folder 140/2)
    - Part (Box-folder 58/6)
  - I'll be around, Alec Wilder
    - Part (bass), On folder: Arr. ideas for Q (Box-folder 64/4)
  - I'll take romance
    - Lead sheets; part (tenor saxophone) (Box-folder 53/6)
  - I'll write you a poem
    - Parts, Gary McFarland arrangement (Box-folder 41/5)
  - I'm getting sentimental over you, George Bassman
    - Score; sketches (Concert Jazz Band), Inscribed: For CJB, 12/4/64 (Box-folder 121/1)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 30/4)
  - I'm getting tired of dreaming
    - Sketches, From "Misc. works, some for Count Basie Band" folder (Box-folder 19/3)
  - I'm gone
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 128/6)
  - I'm gonna go fishin', Duke Ellington
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Bill Holman arrangement (Box-folder 123/1)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Bill Holman arrangement (Box-folder 34/4)
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 16/7)
  - Imps and demons
    - Score; sketches (orchestra), On folder: In progress (Box-folder 140/6)
    - Sketch; parts (orchestra), Date on baritone saxophonepart: Sept 1, 1989 (Box-folder 67/10)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
  - In a mist, Bix Beiderbeck
    - Lead sheets, Yale Jazz Festival, 1988; On folder: GM parts, Kelly and Mike's tunes (Box-folder 67/7)
    - Lead sheet, Laid in: correspondence to Billy Taylor regarding arrangement, 1994 February 26 (Box-folder 23A/17)
  - In a sentimental mood, Duke Ellington
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 129/1)
    - Parts (baritone saxophone), GM personal performance parts and bass part (Box-folder 116)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 45/1)
    - Lead sheets, Yale Jazz Festival, 1988; On folder: GM parts, Kelly and Mike's tunes (Box-folder 67/7)
  - In the service of the I.R.S.
    - Sketch score; parts (band), On folder: 1 chorus, for Miami Univ. Band (Box-folder 131/10)
    - Sketch scores; parts (band), Alternate title on score: Stan and Ollie (A fine mess for) (Box-folder 131/11)
  - In this superior establishment
    - Lead sheet with lyrics, From the play/musical Happy Birthday (Box-folder 13/6)
  - Inaugural celebration '93, Includes: Arkansas traveler; Heartbreak Hotel
    - Score; part (baritone saxophone), Tom Scott arrangement; Laid in: note from Tom Scott to GM (Box-folder 23A/2)
  - Innocent (never learned)
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Mike Carubia arrangement (Box-folder 128/3)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 40/3)
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 15/6)
    - Lead sheet, For the Mel Tormé vocal compilation "Tentet with Tormé" (Box-folder 62/6)
  - Interwoven
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Manny Album arrangement (Box-folder 122/7)
  - Intro and fanfare
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 140/7)
  - Intro for something (misc. intros folder)
    - Sketch, On folder: New intros in progress (Box-folder 140/7)
  - Introspect, From the 1977 film La menace
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Invention, Mitchel Forman
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 13/8)
  - The invitation
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 16/2)
    - Lead sheet, For the Mel Tormé vocal compilation "Tentet with Tormé" (Box-folder 62/6)
  - Iowesya (I owes ya), Milt Jackson
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/1)
  - Israel, John Carisi
    - Score (nonet), John Carisi arrangement (Box-folder 49/3)
    - Parts (tentet) (Box-folder 112/5)
  - It could happen to you
    - Part (baritone saxophone), From "Brubeck parts" folder (Box-folder 82/1)
  - It don't mean a thing, Duke Ellington
    - Part (1st alto saxophone), From "Shorty Rogers" folder (Box-folder 62/2)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/7)
  - It must be Christmas
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Bill Finnegan arrangement (Box-folder 147/3)
    - Score (big band), Ralph Burns arrangement For the recording Holliday with Mulligan (Box-folder 148/1)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Bill Finnegan arrangement (Box-folder 1/3)
    - Parts (big band), Ralph Burns arrangement For the recording Holliday with Mulligan (Box-folder 2/1)
    - Lead sheets; lyric sheet, Lyric sheet by Judy Holliday (Box-folder 12/8)
    - Lead sheets; rhythm parts (Box-folder 12/8)
    - Lead sheet, For the Mel Tormé vocal compilation "Tentet with Tormé" (Box-folder 62/6)
  - It's bad for me, Cole Porter
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Al Cohn arrangement (Box-folder 147/2)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Al Cohn arrangement (Box-folder 1/2)
  - It's gone
    - Lead sheet; sketch (Box-folder 22/18)
    - Lead sheets, From studio session with Scott Hamilton for the recording Soft lights and sweet music (Box-folder 19/17)
  - It's Sandy at the beach
    - Parts (baritone saxophone), GM personal performance parts and bass part (Box-folder 116)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 45/5)
    - Miscellaneous parts and lead sheets (Box-folder 58/8)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
  - It's you, Lee Konitz
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 23A/6)
  - I've got a friend
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 22/25)
  - I gotta right to sing the blues, Harold Arlen; Johnny Mandel arrangement For the recording Holliday with Mulligan
    - Score (big band) (Box-folder 145/3)
    - Parts (big band) (Box-folder 3/3)
  - I've grown accustomed to her face, Frederick Loewe / Alan Jay Lerner
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Incomplete (Box-folder 118/4)
  - I've heard that song before
    - Score (big band with vocal), Lennie Neihaus arrangement (Box-folder 135/6)
  - I've just seen her, Charles Strouse
    - Lead sheets, From studio session with Scott Hamilton for the recording Soft lights and sweet music (Box-folder 19/17)
  - I've never been so low on love, Barry Manilow
    - Lead sheet; parts (piano, baritone saxophone) (Box-folder 19/4)
  - Jambalaya
    - Lead sheet, On folder: GM parts, Kelly and Mike's tunes (Box-folder 67/7)
  - Jeru
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band), Recorded and performed with Mel Tormé (Box-folder 126/5)
    - Score (big band), Jeff Sultanof arrangement; On folder: Claude Thornhill Band arrangement 1949, transcribed from parts by Jeff Sultanof 7/97 (Box-folder 146/4)
    - Score; parts (five horn arrangement), For CBS All Star Jazz Show (Box-folder 137/1)
    - Score; parts (big band), On folder: Gerry Mulligan arr., parts, original copies and score and transposed parts for Smithsonian (Box-folder 145/18)
    - Score; sketches (big band), Published by Gunmar, Inc. (Box-folder 57/6)
    - Score (big band), On folder: Elliott Lawrence Series (Box-folder 131/4)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), On folder: Claude Thornhill, the lost tunes, rec'd from Ken Poston 7/95, Jeru, Sorto Kinda, Rose of Rio Grande (Box-folder 47/1)
    - Parts (big band), GM arrangement for Claude Thornhill (Box-folder 57/6)
    - Parts (baritone saxophone, vocals), GM personal performance parts (Box-folder 116)
    - Parts (sextet) (Box-folder 140/4)
    - Parts; notes about tentet (tentet), From "Gig books" (Box-folder 111/1)
    - Part (drums), From "Standards" folder; On verso: "Carioca" drum part (Box-folder 18/19)
    - Parts (miscellaneous) (Box-folder 160/2)
  - Johnny come lately, Duke Ellington
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 16/7)
  - Joost at the Roost
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Inscribed: For Claude Thornhill, Oct 20, 1948 (Box-folder 120/4)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Inscribed: For Thornhill, ink parts (Box-folder 30/1)
    - Parts (miscellaneous) (Box-folder 160/3)
  - Journey
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 23/5)
  - Jump Monk, Charles Mingus
    - Score (incomplete); parts (big band), Parts as used on recording Charles Mingus and friends in concert (Box-folder 59/6)
  - Jumping bean
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Jumptuns: 1 Life 1
    - Lead sheets, GM's music library title: Jumptuns; Simant (Box-folder 22/21)
  - Just by myself, Benny Golson
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/2)
  - Just in time, Jules Styne
    - Part (baritone saxophone); miscellaneous concert parts, On folder: Art Farmer, Lincoln Center '94, The art of trumpet (Box-folder 24/1)
    - Parts, Incomplete (Box-folder 8/4)
  - Just want to sing and dance like Fred Astaire
    - Score; parts (tentet), Tentet instrumental for "Astaire show" (Box-folder 57/5)
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band), Incomplete parts (Box-folder 118/5)
    - Lead sheets with lyrics (Box-folder 13/2)